

# Curriculum Vitae of: Kelly M. Conway, CPA

## General Background

Since 2003, Ms. Conway has focused her career entirely on investigative auditing and the measurement of damages. She has diversified experience in matters dealing with loss of earnings, stock/inventory losses, third party liability, and arson and fraud.

### Education

Bachelor of Science - 2002 Northern Michigan University Marquette, MI

### Subsequent Accounting Courses – 2004-2005

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, Milwaukee, Wisconsin Carroll College, Waukesha, Wisconsin

### Professional Status

- \*Accountant, Insight Forensic Accountants, S.C.
- \*Certified Public Accountant in Wisconsin
- \*Member, Wisconsin Institute of Certified Public Accountants
- \*Member, American Institute of Certified Public Accountants

## **Professional History**

Insight Forensic Accountants, S.C. (formerly Peters & Associates) - December 2003 to present

## Frank J. Chudy, CPA, Marquette, Michigan, 2002 to 2003

Accounting Assistant – responsibilities included tax preparation assistance, client bank reconciliations, and bookkeeping.

#### **Enright Construction**, Marquette, Michigan, 2002 to 2003

Office Manager – responsibilities included monthly bank reconciliation, rent collections and prepare monthly rent rolls, and manage employee daily time tickets.

In her current position at Insight Forensic Accountants, Ms. Conway is responsible for the evaluation of a variety of damages. Ms. Conway has experience in the review of insurance claims for economic and physical damages in a variety of businesses and industries. She has also provided litigation support services. Specific assignments include work in the following areas:

\*Loss of Income \*Business Income Losses

\*Inventory Losses \*Employee Dishonesty Losses/Theft Losses

\*Extra Expense Measurement \*Subrogation Cases